{
    "quizId": "111111",
    "quizTitle": "MyQuiz",
    "quizDomain": {
        "domainId": 117,
        "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
    },
    "quizDuration": "1",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionId": "541",
            "question": "_____________ property of the Radiobutton in a form indicates the default status of the element",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Default Checked",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Default Checked",
            "option2": "Checked",
            "option3": "Default Value",
            "option4": "Default Selected"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "542",
            "question": "Which is not an attribute of the cookie property?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Host",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Path",
            "option2": "Host",
            "option3": "Secure",
            "option4": "Domain"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "543",
            "question": " What does isNaN function do in JavaScript?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Return true if the argument is not a number.",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Return true if the argument is not a number.",
            "option2": "Return false if the argument is not a number.",
            "option3": "Return true if the argument is a number",
            "option4": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "544",
            "question": " What PHP stands for?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "option2": "Pre Hypertext Processor",
            "option3": "Pre Hyper Processor",
            "option4": "Pre Hypertext Process"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "545",
            "question": " Which of the following tags is not a valid way to begin and end a PHP code block?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "<?php ?>",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "<% %>",
            "option2": "<? ?>",
            "option3": "<?php ?>",
            "option4": "<?= ?>"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "546",
            "question": "What is the difference between XML and HTML?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "XML is used for exchanging data, HTML is not.",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "HTML is used for exchanging data, XML is not.",
            "option2": "XML is used for exchanging data, HTML is not.",
            "option3": "HTML can have user defined tags, XML cannot",
            "option4": "Both b and c above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "547",
            "question": "Which tags are most commonly used by search engines?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Heading",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Heading",
            "option2": "Title",
            "option3": "Paragrah",
            "option4": "All of above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "548",
            "question": "What is the <br> tag for?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Line break",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Space",
            "option2": "Paragraph break",
            "option3": "Line break",
            "option4": "Word break"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "549",
            "question": "What is the attribute for <image> tag?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "src",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "pt",
            "option2": "url",
            "option3": "path",
            "option4": "src"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "550",
            "question": "Each list item in an ordered or unordered list has which tag?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "ol tag",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "list tag",
            "option2": "ls tag",
            "option3": "li tag",
            "option4": "ol tag"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "551",
            "question": "Which of the following tags below are used for a multi-line text input control?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "textarea tag",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "textml tag",
            "option2": "text tag",
            "option3": "textarea tag",
            "option4": " Both b and c above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "552",
            "question": "Which of the following attributes below are used for a font name?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "font",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "fontname",
            "option2": "fn",
            "option3": "font",
            "option4": "face"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "553",
            "question": " What are <div> tags used for?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "To logically divide the document",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "To replace paragraphs. i.e. p tags",
            "option2": "To logically divide the paragraphs",
            "option3": "To logically divide the document",
            "option4": "To provide space between tables"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "554",
            "question": "Which of the following are capable of Java Script functions?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Accepting parameters",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Returning multiple values",
            "option2": "Accepting parameters and returning values",
            "option3": "Accepting parameters",
            "option4": "all of the above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "555",
            "question": "Which of the following is correct to write “Hello World” on the web page?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "document.write(“Hello World”)",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "System.out.println(“Hello World”)",
            "option2": "print(“Hello World”)",
            "option3": "document.write(“Hello World”)",
            "option4": "response.write(“Hello World”)"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "556",
            "question": "Which of the following syntax is correct to refer an external script called “formValidation.js”?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "< script src = “formValidation.js”>",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "< script href = “formValidation.js”>",
            "option2": "< script source = “formValidation.js”>",
            "option3": "< script name = “formValidation.js”>",
            "option4": "< script src = “formValidation.js”>"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "557",
            "question": "What type of image maps could be used with Java Script?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Client-side image maps",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Client-side image maps",
            "option2": "Server-side image maps",
            "option3": "Both",
            "option4": "Localhost image maps"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "558",
            "question": "What is the purpose of <noscript> tag in Java Script?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Prevents scripts on the page from executing.",
            "option2": "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers",
            "option3": "Suppresses the result to be displayed on the web page",
            "option4": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "559",
            "question": "Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Date",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Function",
            "option2": "File",
            "option3": "FileUpload",
            "option4": "Date"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "560",
            "question": "Which of the following is a client-side Java Script object?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "FileUpload",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "File",
            "option2": "Function",
            "option3": "FileUpload",
            "option4": "Time"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "561",
            "question": "If we don’t want the script to write page content, under which HTML tag should the JS tag be placeD?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "< body>",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "< body>",
            "option2": "< head>",
            "option3": "Any of a and b above",
            "option4": "Both b and c above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "562",
            "question": "Which of the following statements are true for Java script?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Both 1 and 2 above",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "JavaScript is case sensitive",
            "option2": "JavaScript statements can be grouped together in blocks",
            "option3": "semicolon at the end of statement is mandatory",
            "option4": "Both 1 and 2 above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "563",
            "question": "Which of the following statements are false for Java script?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Variable names are not case sensitive",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Variable names are not case sensitive",
            "option2": "Variable names must begin with a letter or the underscore character",
            "option3": "Var is used to declare a variable",
            "option4": "Both b and c above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "564",
            "question": " Which of the ways below is incorrect of instantiating a date?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "new Date(dateString)",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "new Date(dateString)",
            "option2": "new Date()",
            "option3": "new Date(seconds)",
            "option4": "new Date(year, month, day, hours, minutes, seconds, milliseconds)"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "565",
            "question": " Which of the following statements are false for Java script?",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "JavaScript cannot be used to create cookies",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "JavaScript can react to events",
            "option2": "JavaScript can read and write HTML elements",
            "option3": "JavaScript cannot be used to create cookies",
            "option4": "Both b and c above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "566",
            "question": "____________ tag simply jumps to the next line.",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "<br>",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "<br>",
            "option2": "<br/>",
            "option3": "</br>",
            "option4": "<break>"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "567",
            "question": "________ sets the font to the specified font name.",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Face",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Font",
            "option2": "Size",
            "option3": "Face",
            "option4": "Color"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "568",
            "question": "The  ____________ layer is pure hardware in any network infrastructure.",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "Physical",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "Physical",
            "option2": "Network",
            "option3": "Transport",
            "option4": " Application"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "569",
            "question": "When any client wishes to communicate with an IS using browser software, the client sends out a broadcast using the Server’s _________________ as the identifier.",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "IP address",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "IP address",
            "option2": "Domain Name",
            "option3": "IP address & Domain name",
            "option4": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "570",
            "question": "_____________ is not a type of lists",
            "difficulty": "EASY",
            "correctOption": "numeric",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 117,
                "domain": "Advanced Web Programming"
            },
            "option1": "unordered",
            "option2": "ordered ",
            "option3": "numeric",
            "option4": "definition"
        }
    ]
}